Previously on This Is Us...
《我的生活》前情提要
- Baby? - ?Something's not right.
-  -有些不
We lost the third baby, Jack.
我失去了第三孩子  杰克
I'm very sorry.
我很z憾
I like to think that
我愿意相信
you took the sourest lemon that life has to offer
你⑸活Ыo你檬般的酸楚
and turned it into something resembling lemonade.
成q如檬汽水般的甘甜
36 years ago, my life started with you leaving me
36年前  我躺在破@子里
on a fire station doorstep.
被你z在消防局
Beth, The man has stage IV stomach cancer.
z  他得了晚期胃癌
Why you watching this stuff?
你槭裁匆看@N玩意
Told them to go screw themselves.
我他L蛋了
I'm moving to New York.
我要搬到~s去
"Show business."
啡Π
Grandma and Grandpa are here!
奶奶砹
I'll be in my room.
我先回房了
This is the scariest part.
最可怕的要砹
Some people think the scariest part
有些人f最可怕的
is coming to the hospital to have the baby.
是磲t院生孩子
Nah. The scariest part
不  最可怕的
is leaving the hospital with the baby.
是е孩子x_t院
- Babies.  - Babies, of course.
-孩子  -孩子
Doc, these two, they only fall asleep
t生  @z只有挨著彼此
if they're next to each other.
才能睡得著
Is that unusual?
@正常
Well, they've been sharing the same hot tub the last nine months;
竟^去九月他都睡一床
you can't bust them up right away.
你不能把他突然分_
No, I'm not concerned.
所以不必心
Did she tell you what we named them?
她有]有跟你f我起的名字
No, actually, she didn't.
不  她]f
You can go ahead and tell him, babe.
你f吧
Kevin, Kate and Kyle.
P文  P特和P
All Ks.
都是P
It's a good letter.
P是好字
We had a good doctor.
因槲有好t生
Right, Bec?
Π  小
I'm sorry.
Σ黄
I'm just, um, a little overwhelmed.
我就是有c]反^
Thank you very much for everything.
xx你所做的一切
Grandma and Grandpa are here!
奶奶砝
Hi, Grandpa.
好
What are you guys doing here?
你怎么^砹
We were on our way into the city
我淙ナ欣
and thought we'd stop by and say hi.
路砀你打招呼
A friend at work gave us his Hamilton tickets.
百老R衢T音
Feel like I'm gonna be the one person
我大概是地球上
on the planet who doesn't like this damn thing.
唯一不喜g@|西的人
- There's a man living with us.  - What?
-有男人跟我一起住  -什么
Daddy's friend from work.
是爸爸的同事
Come play Legos!
硗娣e木吧
Yeah, come play Legos with us.
快砀我玩e木吧
We're coming, we're coming.
砹砹
I missed you.
好想你
This was not the plan.
不是@拥
What plan?
什么
The plan for how I was gonna tell her that I found him.
怎么告V她我找到他了
I wasn't aware there was a plan for that, babe.
我不知道你有
Well, there was.
有的
I mean, there was gonna be.
本泶蛩阌的
The plan was forming, but now it's off.
本碓谥贫ㄓ  F在]蛄
Okay, so what are you gonna do now?
好吧  那你打算怎么k
Right now? ?
F在
I'm gonna put on a fake-ass smile.
我打算假b微笑
I'm gonna ask to speak to my mother privately.
然后要求跟我为f
And then I'm gonna tell her something
我告V她一件
that's gonna completely and utterly devastate her.
她震@到缀醣⒌氖
Can I talk to you privately?
能为跟你聊聊
- One second.  - ?Sure.
-一就好  -然
Everybody...
大家好
Holy hangover.
死的宿醉
*And faces, and friendly faces*
*和  友善的*
*And still I had to be free*
*我仍f向往自由*
*I've been to paradise*
*我曾去^天堂*
*But I've never been to...*
*但我不曾...*
?How's your face?
你的好
Well, it's fine.
好
Luckily, I have all this fat to soften the blow.
好我有脂肪砭解_
Stop that.
ef了
How's your breakfast?
早餐怎么
You mean this, uh, steel-cut oatmeal
你f@
and egg white pancake with no salt, no sugar,
你o我吃的@N粗切燕
and no oil that you're making me eat?
和o}o糖o油的u蛋煎
Yes.
是的
It's amazing.
太好吃了
Right? ?
是吧
It's the best thing I've ever tasted.
@是我吃^最美味的食物
Quick question.
}
last night, after the party...
昨天晚上  派Y束之后
I kind of blacked out.
我有c嗥了
We didn't...
我]有...
Oh, no.
]有
A lot of vomiting
除了大吐特吐
but not a lot of anything else.
e的什么都]做
Oh. Sexy.
蚩
You have an amazing voice, by the way.
α  你的音真好
I did not know that you sang.
我不知道你唱歌
Well, I did not know
我也不知道
that you spy on people in the bathroom.
你喜g偷看e人洗澡
Will you sing for me?
能再槲页一段
No.
不行
Come on, Kate, come on.
戆  P特  戆
Come on, come on. You're good.
戆  戆  你唱得很好
And I'm not talking about karaoke-good.
我f的好不是卡拉OK水
I'm talking good-good.
而是I水实暮
Have-- did-- you-- did...
你曾...
Did you ever perform?
你上_表演^
When I was really young.
我很小的r候
Cyndi Lauper was kind of my jam.
美造歌手
"Time after Time" cover was...
《反反汀纺唱片真是...
I rocked it. I was, you know...
我太拿手了  我曾...
I rocked it like it was my job.
直就像我自己的歌一
?But then I grew up.
但是后砦议L大了
And then I grew...
S著我...
and, um, you know,
然后你懂的
I try to avoid the spotlight.
我就_始回避聚光袅
- Are you done? ? - Yes.
-你吃完了  -吃完了
Are you?
你吃完了
One more song.
再硪皇
- One more song. - Okay, Kate,
-再硪皇  -P特
I am super pumped about this move to New York City.
我太激玉R上就要搬去~s了
I mean, we've got a ton to figure out,
然我有一大堆事情要解Q
of course, but I'm super pumped.
但我非常激
Wait... that was real?
等等  你是碚娴
Yeah. Stage acting, it's my new jam. Oh...
然  舞_  @是我的新路子
Do you think you could get that really cute, uh,
你X得你能系上那特e可鄣
that theater casting director,
特e喜g我的
- the one who liked me. What's... - Cara.
-舞_⌒翘  她叫...-卡拉
Cara, yes. I love Cara... Yeah.
卡拉  ]e  我劭拉
and when you get her on the phone,
等你打通了她的
tell her I'm only interested in doing heavy drama.
得告V她  我只φ「信d趣
We're not moving all the way to New York City
我一路折v到~s
so I can do some lame off-Broadway comedy.
不是榱搜菀恍┓前倮R的垃圾喜
You want me to go with you?
你想我跟你一起去
Of course. Yeah.
然
There's no way I could do this without you.
]有你我什么事情都做不了
and maybe you should specify that I don't want to
也S你得跟他明_
do anything where I have to show my penis.
我不想做任何需要展示我的u巴的事
Toby.
托比
I didn't see you there, man. What's up?
我不知道你也在@  老兄  怎么了
How's this? You know what we should do?
@好吃  你知道我要做什么
We should look into the Meatpacking District.
我去曼哈D肉^看看
It's like an up and coming.
前途o量啊
Pancakes are good.
煎很不e
Is she making you eat this?
她逼你吃@N|西
I'm trying to have some sex.
我在取和她上床
So now he's been here for about a week.
他砑依锟煲恢芰
I guess I just wanted to get used to the idea of him myself,
我想著去T他@人的存在
you know, before I told you,
之后再把@事告V你
and this has nothing to do with you or Dad--
但@c你和爸爸]有任何P系
I hope you know that.
我希望你能理解
I do know that, yes, of course. ?Okay, okay.
我能理解  我然理解  好了
I mean, obviously, I've been curious about him
很@然  我暮苄〉r候
since I was a kid.
就λ感到好奇
And I know you guys would have found him if you could have.
我知道你如果能找的早就找到他了
So who is he?
那么他是l
What did he tell you about himself?
他的身世和你f^多少
His name is William.
他叫威廉
That's it?
只有名字
He didn't tell you anything else? ?
他]告V你e的事
He has a cat.
他B了一只
Stomach cancer.
他得了胃癌
It's the basic gist of what I know so far.
目前橹刮抑恢道@些
Well, where is he?
他在哪呢
I'd like to, uh, meet him.
我想他
- He's in Annie's room, but... - ?Okay.
-他在安妮的房g  可是...  -好的
I don't know if he's ready for company, Ma.
我不知道他是否浜靡客人
Hold on one second.
等一下
Okay.
好了
Car seats are installed.
汽座椅安好了
Policeman approved.
警察批柿
I'll pull up, we'll load up.
我把_^  然后上
And then the adventure begins, yeah?
我的冒U拇司烷_始了  好
Okay.
好的
If I were you, I would head right to Mexico.
我要是你就^也不回地去墨西哥
If I don't come back, at least you'll know where to find me.
要是我]回  你至少知道去哪找我
Wait.
等等
Okay, let's lock and load.
好了  快上吧
Here, I got him. ?Yeah.
我抱他
Oh. Come on, big boy.
戆  大男孩
Okay.
好了
- I wanted to introdu... - ?Hi.
-我想o你介B...  -你好
I'm Rebecca, I'm Randall's mother.
我是卡  m德的
Very nice to meet you.
很高dJR你
Nice to meet you, as well.
我也很高dJR你
Sweetheart, could you give us just a moment to chat?
H鄣  能我z为
Yeah.
好的
Thank you.
xx
You look well.
你馍不e
It's okay, my little lady.
e害怕  我的小美女
He's not taking my breast.
他不喝我的奶
We just go put her over and wreathe her.
我把她翻^  然后裹住她
Can you help with him, please? He's being really fussy.
臀野  他太y哄了
We have burping cloths. Look in their bedroom.
家里有嘴  去他的P室找找
It's not... there's not... in here.
]找到  不在@
Please, just come back in here.
你快回戆
- I need you to help me, please. - Okay.
-快臀  -好的
Are you laying down, Jack? ?
你躺下了  杰克
Can you please check on Kevin?
你去看看P文好
Why, why won't he stop crying?
槭裁  他槭裁纯不停
They'll be in college soon.
他一D眼就上大W了
?Which one?
是哪
Probably the one that hates me.
大概是我的那吧
- He doesn't hate you. - Jack,
-他不你  -杰克
I think we're gonna have to start him on formula.
我想我得_始喂他奶粉了
No. He's fine.
不用  他很好
He won't take to my breast.
他不喝我的奶
We have to treat them the same.
我得用相同的方式Υ他
He's not the same.
可他并不相同
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Σ黄  Σ黄
He's just... He's not.
他不一
I grew the other two  inside of me,
另外孩子是在我肚子里L大的
and he feels like a stranger.
可他s像外人
And I feel really terrible for saying that out loud,
m然@么f我真的很y^
but he just... he does.
可我真的@么J
Jack,
杰克
when we were leaving the hospital...
我x_t院的r候
I know. You were having second thoughts about bringing him home.
我知道  你考]^不他回家
It's fine.
]P系的
- No. No, it's not that. I...  - It's natural.
-不  不是@拥  -@很正常
He's fine, Bec.
他]}  小
He's fine.
他]}的
Look at us.
你看我z
I mean, I was a complete stranger.
我以前也就是陌生人
Look how quickly I took to your breast.
但你的胸不也很快被我攻下了
You're an idiot. ?
你就是笨蛋
Yeah. I'm your idiot.
Π  我是你的小笨蛋
Okay?
行了吧
And they are our babies.
他是我的孩子
He's our baby.
他也是我的孩子
Okay?
好
They'll be in college soon?
他很快就去上大W了吧
Any day now.
指日可待
And then she just asked to speak to him alone.
然后她就f要和他为了
- About what? - I don't know.
-什么呢  -我不知道
Whatever biological fathers and adopted mothers talk about.
就H生父H和B母的事吧
- What is that? - The Knicks,
NBA尼克斯命名由
Beth. How the hell am I supposed to know?
z  我怎么知道他在什么
I...
我...
You love me so much that you're just gonna give me that one?
你@么畚  你一定o我HH的
You know me so well, my friend.
你真了解我  朋友
I got to take him to that doctor's appointment in two hours.
再^尚r我要他去看t生
God. What the hell do you think
天啊  你X得
- they're talking about, anyway? - I don't know, honey.
-他究竟什么  -我不知道  H鄣
He found me.
是他找到我的
- He brought me here. - But you stayed.
-他我磉@  -但是你在@鹤×
Yes, I stayed. ?
是的  我住下了
We had a deal.
我之前s定好的
I won't tell him, if that's what you're thinking.
我不告V他的  如果你心@的
Oh, God. All those...
天啊  那一切...
It will break him.
他崩⒌
It will. Knowing that he could've known you
^  要是他知道他本可以JR你
and that I kept him from that.
s被我M中阻r了
Rebecca, the deal we made was the right one.
卡  我的s定是明智之e
For everyone.
γ人都好
- If you hurt him... - ?I won't.
-如果你敢害他...  -我不的
Fine, then.
那就好
But know this
不^你住
my son,
我鹤
who I raised,
我狃B成人的他
is gonna put everything he has into trying to save you,
肯定竭M全力砭饶
because that's who he is.
因檫@就是他的槿
It's gonna come in front of his job,
他把@事看得比工作重要
in front of his marriage,
也比婚姻更重要
and in front of his time with his kids.
甚至比他在家陪孩子重要
So you better damn well be worth that.
所以你最好不要辜他
Damn it.
死的
Yes, um, it would be for an open-ended reservation,
是  在我退租到房子之前
until we can find him a rental.
都要o限期地A@房g
And your pillows are hypoallergenic, yeah?
你那旱恼眍^不^敏吧
And can I just confirm that the hotel gym's not just, like,
有我想_J下酒店的健身房
three crappy elliptical machines?
不只有三_f跑步C吧
'Cause he needs space for floor work and exercise
因樗需要龅刈龈┡P沃的
- and free weight... - Great.
-有力量...  -很好
You know, actually, can I just have pictures sent to me?
或者  你方便l照片o我看下
Have you seen my keys?
你看我匙了
I think you left 'em in the plan you never made.
匙估落在你那空^里了吧
So she's funny, too. That's good. My keys.
你挺幽默  不e啊  匙在@耗
So?
怎么
He seems very nice.
他人很好
Honey,
H鄣
we should get going if we're gonna get dinner
要在市^吃晚的
in the city first. ?Oh.
我得so走了
- I bet the tunnel's gonna be jammed. - ?Okay.
-我敢f那隧道肯定堵  -好吧
No, stay!
不要  留下砺
Dad's work friend doesn't eat a lot.
爸爸的同事吃不了多少的
- You can have some of his dinner. - What?
-你可以吃他那份  -真的
Grandma and Grandpa can't stay, girls.
奶奶要走了  女
And, anyway, i've got an appointment with my work friend, so,
r且一何液屯事有事要出去呢
I promise to catch up with you about all this.
我保C后面找你好好聊一聊的
Promise?
f好咯
Miguel, ?thanks for dropping by unexpectedly.
米格  感x你的不期而至
Rewind. Thanks for dropping by.
重f  感x路拜L
Always love it. Always love you guys. Peace.
超圻@招  永h勰哦  再
He's hiding something.
他在[m什么
Hey. We got to get goin'.
我走了
William?
威廉
William. Where you goin'?
威廉  你要去哪
- Home. - Why? What happened?
-回家  -槭裁  l生了什么事
- We got the doctor's appointment. - You should cancel.
-我As了t生的  -你取消
Why would I cancel... W-Will you get in the damn car?
我槭裁匆取消...  你能上
I knew if I told you I was leaving, you'd try and stop me
我知道如果我告V你我要x_  你阻止我
like you are right now.
正像F在@
You'd try and stop me
你O法阻止我
'cause you were raised to be a good man.
是因槟愀改附逃你要做好人
But I wasn't the one who raised you that way, Randall.
但那羽B育你的人不是我  m德
I was reminded of that today.
我今天想起砹
That you have parents.
你有父母
That I just can't step in 40 years later
我不能在四十年后突然出F
and enjoy the fruits of someone else's labor.
坐享e人的映晒
So, just like that, you go?
就@恿  你要走
No good-bye to the girls?
不跟孩子告e
- The girls will be fine. - No, they'll be devastated.
-她]事的  -不  她很y^
They don't even know who I am.
她B我是l都不知道
- Look, this doctor... - He isn't gonna
-著  @t生...-他要f的
tell me anything I don't already know.
我早就知道了
- But he might. - ?He won't.
-但有可能  -不的
But he might.
有可能
And something tells me he might be a little more thorough
而且我X得他比
than the doctor at whatever free homeless clinic
你在哪免M流釉\所找的庸t
you've been going to to get your free medical counsel at.
更了解你的病情
To say nothing of the fact that I had to kiss up
更不用f榱湍泐As到他
to the biggest D-bag at my firm
我不得不去找公司里^混蛋
just to get you this appointment.
拍R屁好他
So, yes, William,
所以]e  威廉
you are getting in the car right now,
你F在就得上
and we are going to this doctor's appointment.
然后我去@位t生
And then and only then will I give you permission
然后我才能允S你
to hobble off like Hobo Joe without saying
招呼都不打一  就像流浪h一
so much as a good-bye.
一瘸一拐地走掉
Startin' to not feel so bad
把你G在消防局@件事
about leaving you at that fire station.
F在]那么我感到愧疚了
Yeah, whatever.
S便吧
Hi, white people.
白人
Friendly neighborhood black man.
我只是友好的黑人居
Kate, can I get one right here?
P特  能在@拍一
Kate? Right here? Can I just get one right here?
P特  就在@  能o你拍一
Kate? Who are you wearing?
P特  你穿的什么牌子
- Kate? Kate? - What are you doing?
-P特  P特  -你在干什么
Is it true that you're dating Taylor Swift?
你真的在和泰勒・斯威夫特s
Is it true that you just broke up
你真的和泰勒・斯威夫特
with Taylor Swift just now?
分手了
What are you doing?
你在做什么
Give me just one day.
o我一天rg
One day where you're the star.
今天你是明星
Hey, where are you? I've called you, like, ten times.
你在哪  我o你打了十泶坞了
Listen, um... Can we just hire one of those services
著  我能雇人兔
that comes in and, you know, packs everything for you?
砑依锎虬|西
I think Jason Momoa told me about a guy who does that.
我得杰森・莫告V我有人ｉT干@
Let's get that number from Momoa's office.
我so找莫k公室的人他的
His assistant. That, uh...
他的助理...
Dahala Mapuana, I think her name was.
_哈拉・普哈{  她好像叫@
Or was it Patty?
要不就是帕蒂
You remember Jason Momoa. He's the, uh...
你得杰森・莫吧  他是...
he's the original Dothraki guy.
他演的那土著多斯拉克人
We met him at Seth Green's house. Where are you, all right?
我在斯・格林家^他  你在哪
I'm getting overwhelmed. Pick up the phone.
我快受不了了  so接
Where are we going? ?
我@是去哪
Well, no more background singing for you.
e再偷偷唱歌了
Your voice is way too beautiful
你的音太美妙了
to only be heard in a bathroom.
只能在l生g到太可惜了
Today is your day, babe.
今天你是主角
We are on our way to your first big gig.
我正往你的第一演出F鲎
- What? - ?Yep, I, uh... I downloaded
-什么  -]e  我下d了
an instrumental copy of "Time after Time,"
《反反汀返陌樽嘁
found an old boom box.
找到老式手提音C
It's showtime, baby! ?
表演rg到  H鄣
Toby, there is no way in hell
托比  我^Σ
that I'm gonna sing in front of people.
在一群人面前唱歌的
Well, then you'll be depriving the world.
那你就辜了整世界
Well, the world will live.
那世界不有什么p失
Yes, but your audience may not.
]e  可你的sp失了
All right.
到了
?What the hell?
搞什么鬼
Okay, so,
好了
my Aunt Dolly actually lives here.
我的多莉姑姑就住在@里
All right, I booked you in their prime slot, 3:00 p.m.
我湍慵s了下午三c的S金到Lrg
It's right after Jell-O but before their nap.
在他吃果鲋后  午睡之前
Perfect place to break your seal, right?
首演的^佳地c吧
Now, remember, most of 'em will probably be asleep.
住  大多等丝赡芏蓟杌栌睡了
The rest won't remember this tomorrow.
]睡的人明天也忘得一干二
And most of them lived through World War II,
而且他大多都v^二
so no matter how bad you are, they've seen worse.
所以o你唱得有多  他都不介意
Come on.
戆
I'm sorry, do you need the red carpet?
抱歉  需要槟沅t毯
- No. - ?Okay, come on.
-不用  -好了  戆
Well, now,
瞧瞧
all three of these babies are looking very good, Jack.
三看上去都很棒  杰克
Very strong, very healthy.
延纸】
Okay, good. That's good. 'Cause some-sometimes
那就好  那就好  因橛r候
one does something different than the other two.
一的行楹土硗不同
You just... you start spinnin' a little... ?
你就...  胡思y想
They're all doing very well.
他都非常健康
Okay.
好吧
How are you guys doing?
你z最近如何
We're great. We're good. We're, um...
不e  是的  我...
tired but, uh, good.
很疲v  但不e
And Rebecca?
卡怎么
I mean, I only ask because
我@么
it's a little unusual for the father to be here alone.
是因楦赣H一般不为Ш⒆磲t院
She just needed a little break, you know?
她只是需要好好休息一下
She's... she's... she's not totally herself.
她...  她有c不在B
I mean, she's a...
她有c...
little dazed,I guess?
有c茫然  我猜吧
She's not bonding with the babies.
她跟不H近
And not with Kyle, mainly. You know? Not with Kyle.
尤其是P  她跟P不H
I think she might be a little broken.
她可能是有些崩⒘
You know, I-I think the babies might have broken my wife.
好像我妻子崩⒘
You can fix her, right?
你能治好她吧
Or you can tell me how to fix her? I was... I was hoping
或者告V我怎么治好她  我指望...
- you could tell me how to fix her. - Sit down, Jack.
-你能告V我怎么治好她  -坐下  杰克
She lost a baby, Jack.
她失去了一孩子  杰克
You can't just dismiss that.
你不能忽略@件事
- So did I. ?- Yeah.
-我也一  -
And you took your grief, and you... channeled it into action.
可你化悲樾恿
You willed yourself forward with positivity,
以eO的B度跨^了那道坎
but Rebecca has just...
但卡...
She's gonna have to do this in her own way,
她必以自己的方式度^@P
and you're just gonna have to give her the space to do it.
而你只能要o她足虻目臻g
Yeah. What if she doesn't find her way?
如果她找不到k法呢
- She will. - ?How do you know?
-她找到的  -你怎么知道
For the same reason that I know
正如同我知道
you're gonna give her the space to find it.
你o她足虻目臻g
'Cause I believe in good people.
因槲蚁嘈拍都是善良之人
so you got to take everything I say with a grain of salt.
所以我f的  你最好e全信
Now, look, there's a couch in there in my office.
我k公室里有沙l
Why don't you go lie down, take a nap?
不如你去那躺躺睡X
I'm-I'm totally free the rest of the day.
我今天一整天都很e
I can use the time with my namesakes.
正好可以陪陪@些小家伙
No, there's three. You don't... you don't...
不了  他三呢  你不...
I brought them into the world, Jack.
我H手把他У竭@世上  杰克
I am perfectly qualified to sit here and watch 'em sleep
我^τ匈Y格花仔r坐在@里
and crap themselves for a couple of hours.
看他睡X和拉屎
Now go. Now.
去睡吧  走吧
Hi. Sorry to bother you. I'm looking for someone.
你好  抱歉打_了  我在找人
he's Afro-American, very, very thin.
他是美黑人  非常消瘦
Possibly on drugs.
可能是a君子
You know what? I sound ridiculous.
是算了  我太可笑
Sorry. I sound so stupid.
Σ黄  我真是傻透了
You mean Shakespeare? You looking for him?
你是指莎士比  你在找他
Come on, get in.
戆  上
All right. Uh, good afternoon, ladies and germs.
好啦  女士先生  下午好
Uh, my name is Toby.
我叫托比
I'm actually, uh, Dolly's nephew.
其呢  我是多莉的侄子
Everybody knows Aunt Dolly, right?
大家都JR"多莉姑姑"  Π
Wave for everybody, Dolly. Hello, Dolly!
跟大家招招手  多莉  你好啊  多莉
Be careful, gentlemen. She's a real man-eater.
小心c啊  男士  她Ω赌腥撕苡幸惶
Aren't you, Dolly?
是不是啊  多莉
Okay. Okay, well, we have a very
好了  今天下午
special treat for you this afternoon.
我淞艘鎏e表演
The lady that I am about to introduce
我⒁出的@位女士
Adele admires her, Streisand considers her a friend,
阿黛仰慕她  史翠珊把她做朋友
J. Lo wishes she had that ass.
洛佩都w慕她的SM身材
Ladies and gentlemen, performing for one song only,
女士先生  H演唱一首歌
I give you... Kate!
有...  P特
All right, here we go.
戆
That's for you.
o你
- Really? You want me to...? - ?Yup.
-真的  你想我...  -]e
*Lying in my bed I hear the clock tick*
*躺在床上  著[滴答*
*And think of you*
*想著你*
*Caught up in circles*
*D反*
*Confusion is nothing new*
*困惑  早已以槌*
*Flashback to warm nights*
*起那些嘏的夜晚*
*Almost left behind*
*缀跻驯煌*
*Suitcase of memory*
*bM回的行囊*
*Time after*
*一次又一次*
*Sometimes you picture me*
*有r你想起我*
*You're calling to me*
*你呼局我*
*And I can't hear*
*我s不*
*What you've said*
*你f了什么*
*And you say, go slow*
*你f走慢些*
Hey. I'm looking for Shakespeare.
我想找莎士比
*I fall behind*
*我落后了*
*The drum beats out of time*
*鼓得不是r候*
*If you're lost you can look and you will find me*
*若你迷路了  你可以找我  你找到我*
*Time after time*
*一次又一次*
*If you fall I will catch you*
*如果你跌倒了  我扶起你*
*I'll be waiting*
*我等著*
*Time after time*
*一次又一次*
*If you fall I will catch you*
*如果你跌倒了  我扶起你*
*I'll be waiting*
*我等著*
*Time after time*
*一次又一次*
Yeah! Come on!
好棒
Give it up! ?
鼓掌
Oh. Oh, if I had known.
如果我早知道
I would have... I would have
我就...  我就
taken you to the nursing home for every date.
每天你眇B老院了
- Shut up. ?- Okay.
-]嘴  -好吧
No. No, no, just shut it off.
不  不  不  斓
?Just shut it off!
斓
What?
什么事
- Oh, my sister was so right about... - Elaine's here.
-我妹]fe...  -伊R恩在@
She's trashing the joint. I'm locked in the closet.
她在摔|西  我被i在壁焕锪
Insane Elaine? Why is she there?
女人伊R恩  她怎么在那
I called her.
我打o她的
How?
怎么
I deleted her number from your contacts.
我把她的哪闶C上h了
I found it in the Cloud.
我脑浞堇镎业降
You called Insane Elaine?
你系了女人伊R恩
And I had sex with her.
我和她上了床
And I told her I was moving to New York,
我告V她我要搬去~s
- and then she went crazy. - I am not crazy!
-然后她就l了  -我]
Why does everyone call me crazy?! Why?!
槭裁此有人都f我是子  槭裁
You know what? Um, I got a little overwhelmed with the move,
搬家的事我有些不知所措了
you know, I tried calling you, but you're not picking up.
我一直在o你打  可你]接
Oh, God.
天
You know what? She's breaking things again. Get over here.
她又在摔|西了  快^
I will be right over.
我R上^
I am...
我...
I'm sorry. I have to go.
Σ黄  我得走了
Oh, but really, you don't,
你其]必要^去
and it's kind of crazy that you think that you do.
你X得你必^去  @酉胪Ο狂的
Toby, you don't get it.
托比  你不懂
We're-we're twins. We're not like regular people.
我是p胞胎  跟常人不一
When I was a kid, broke my arm
我小r候摔喔觳
and he cried out in pain ten miles away, right?
他在十英里之外的地方疼哭了  懂
We're that connected.
我就是那么o密相B
I thought we were, too, is the thing.
}是我以槲也是如此
Kate, I'm not some nut job who performs grand gestures
P特  我又不是子
for every girl that I go on a few dates with.
S便橐s^状的女生弄@么大排
I like you, Kate. I like you a lot.
我喜g你  P特  我很喜g你
But I can't... I can't play second banana to your brother.
但我做不到跟在你哥后面做男二
You have to.
你只能@
Everyone has to.
所有人都得@
Great.
好吧
Have a good time in New York!
在~s玩得_心
William, will you join me out here?
威廉  能磉@
William.
威廉
Randall. I wish I had better news.
m德  我也希望能砗孟息
The cancer has metastasized
癌胞D移了
to a point where there's really not much we can do.
F在的情r  我也勰能助了
There are some experimental treatments.
F在有一些治方案
Frankly, they haven't been very promising.
f  效果]有太大保障
I'm not very well, as you can probably tell.
我r不太好  你看得出
The baby didn't come from this.
孩子不是@些|西的a物
It came from love.
是矍榈慕Y晶
His mother?
他
You know, we-we... we met on that bus, actually.
我是在那v巴士上相遇的
My world spun on every axis that day.
我的世界都@著那一天旋D
I read poetry to her the first time we talked.
第一次聊天r  我樗x了
Uh, not any of mine.
不是我的
I was too shy for that.
我太害羞了
One of my favorite poets, and...
是我最喜g的人之一
She used to love it when I read to her.
她那r非常喜g我xo她
So what'd you name the baby?
你o孩子取了什么名字
Kyle.
P
I was having triplets, and, um,
我蚜巳胞胎
on a whim, actually, we just decided to name them.
我就是一rd起取了名字
Kevin, Kate and Kyle.
P文  P特和P
I... I lost one of the babies during delivery,
分娩^程中  我失去了一孩子
but your baby showed up
但你的孩子
at the hospital the very same morning.
正好是那天早上出F在了t院
It felt like destiny.
就像命中注定一
Um... I just...
我...
I appreciate this. I-I, um...
能到你  我很感激
I wanted to know his story.
我之前很想知道他的v
And that there was good here, so...
@些就蛄  所以...
I wonder if I could check on him from time to time.
我能r不r去看看他
No. No.
不  不行
I-I also need to know...
我需要_定
I need to know that you're not gonna come back for him.
我需要_定你不碚宜
I need to know that I can move forward.
我需要_定我能松下@口饬
Because he will have your blood
因樗流著你的血
and the blanket you wrapped him up in, but that's it.
睡在你o他包上的毯子里  但到此橹沽
That's the deal. Otherwise, I...
就H此而已了  不然我...
I understand.
我了解
Okay.
好
I'm not...
我和...
I'm not bonding with the baby.
我和那孩子不太H
I want to love him like he's my own,
我想鬯  λ如己出
but every time I look at his face...
但每我看著他的...
Give him his own name.
取一儆谒的名字
What was the name of the poet you used to read to her?
你o她x的  那作者叫什么
Your favorite poet.
你最喜g的人
Thank you.
xx你
How'd it go?
M展如何
It's bad.
不好
Nothing to be done, really.
t生也束手o策  真的
Some experimental treatments
o了治方案
that'll give him a few more months.
可以他再多活月
He's upstairs resting.
他正在巧闲菹
Peacefully with his arms crossed over his chest, no doubt.
平o地㈦p手交叉放在胸前
I have no idea how I came from that man.
我岩勺约菏遣皇撬H生的
I'm so sorry, babe.
我很z憾  H鄣
Yeah, I don't know what I expected.
我也不知道自己在期待什么
Yes, I do.
不  我知道
I expected to find a father who wasn't so damn sick.
我希望我找到的父H]有身患重病
- Randall... - I should have looked for him years ago, Beth.
-m德  -我早c去找他  z
I mean, the girls could have had a grandfather all this time.
@雍⒆就可以和多相啄
Instead, I brought him here so they could what?
可我F在把他接回家是榱耸裁
Fall in love with a dying man.
孩子喜g上一垂死的人
So, this is about the girls, then?
所以你只是心孩子
You don't want them to fall in love with him?
你不希望她喜g上他
He's been here a week, baby.
他到@里都一周了
And you don't know any more about him
你λ的了解
than you did the first time he walked through that door.
也并]有S著@段rg的相而加深
I don't know what you were looking for with all this,
我不知道你做@些事是榱耸裁
or even if you do,
即使你自己知道
but I do know you don't have a whole lot of time.
我也只想f  你的rg和精力是有限的
- Is she gone? - ?Yeah.
-她走了  -走了
God, I hope the booty call was worth it.
我希望你@炮s得值
It was.
值
I just started to get overwhelmed, you know?
我突然得有些不知所措
Started reading one of those plays you gave me.
我x了一本你o我的”
You actually read one?
你才x了一本
I read them all, actually.
事上我全x了
But, uh, this one, though, it's really good, you know?
但是@一本  特e出色
Like, really good.
真的很出色
And I just started to get a little overwhelmed
于是我有c不知所措
'cause I felt like, um,
因槲遗
I felt like maybe it was too good for me.
我怕自己配不上@么好的
It's not, Kevin.
]有  P文
It's not-- they would be lucky.
真的  你能出演是他的福
Well...
好吧...
So my guy turned out to be more insane than Elaine.
我lF我交往的ο蟊纫寥R恩狂
- Toby? - ?Get this.
-托比  -我f
So he takes me to a nursing home...
他把我去一家B老院...
to sing in front of old people.
我在一群老人前唱歌
So I'd be a star but in a comfortable environment,
好我在避免擂蔚那r下一回明星
'cause otherwise I would freak out.
要不然我肯定崩
It was the whole works.
一切都很完美
He had the red carpet, he had the car, suit.
他淞思t毯  豪有Y服
- It was like... - Oh, that's good.
-那一切...  -很棒啊
Yeah. And then afterwards,
是的  在那之后
like, I was on a high, like,
我十分d^
I know it sounds stupid, but I, I felt so free.
m然@起砗苌  但我感X很自由
Then what happened?
然后呢
Well, you called.
你打砹穗
Told him I had to go and he got pouty and mean.
我f我要走  弄得他饧
Wait a minute, I called at that very moment
等一下  我竟然在那NPIr刻黼
and you actually answered the phone?
而你竟然接了
Of course I answered.
我然接啊
Anyway, I need to focus on losing weight
反正我得Ｗ⒌阶约旱p肥事I
and our big move to New York,
有我的~s羯
and I don't even need to be in a relationship.
我根本不需要
You're fired.
你被炒了
What?
什么
Yeah, Kate, you're fired.
]e  P特  你被解雇了
Why?
槭裁窗
You're the personal assistant to your brother, all right?
你是你哥的私人助理
A brother who locks himself in his master bedroom closet.
一把自己P在主P壁焕锏母绺
A master bedroom closet
@壁挥智『
that happens to have a mini-bar in it.
附е一小酒吧
Maybe it's time we go at it alone for a while, you know?
也S我各自^斗自己的事I了
Just for a little while to see what happens.
就一段rg  看Y果如何
You know, maybe we need to grow up a bit.
也S我成熟一c
I don't really know who I am if I'm not your sister.
不做你妹妹  我都不知道自己是l
I do.
我知道
You're gonna love her.
你肯定喜g她的
I don't like it when you're sweet.
我不喜g你b暖男
Okay, I'm here. What?
我砹  什么事
I'm sorry.
Σ黄
Yeah, well, sorry doesn't change the fact...
好吧  但是道歉不能改...
What you did for me today was the nicest thing
]有人像你今天@
that anyone has ever done for me.
槲疫@么用心^
Okay, but that still doesn't...
好吧  但是...
And I'm not moving to New York.
我不打算搬到~s了
- Okay, but that still doesn't change... - I got you something.
-但是改不了...-我槟淞诉@
I accept your apology.
我接受你的道歉
- Yeah? - ?Yes.
-是  -是的
Don't you dare answer that.
不式与
I'm not.
我不接
- Do not. - ?I won't.
-e接  -我不接
Leave a message for Kate.
留言oP特吧
Oh, Kate, good. You didn't answer.
P特  很好  你]接
Hopefully, that means you're having sex.
希望@表示你正"性"福著呢
Anyway, I did it.
f  我I票了
I-I booked a red-eye to New York.
我了去~s的夜g航班
I'm just gonna do it, 'cause, you know...
我打算去了  因...
Kate, if we keep talking about it,
P特  如果我^m下去
we'll talk ourselves out of it.
就褡约e@么做
I'll never go.
我不去
You'll never stay, so...
你不留下  所以...
And I'm not gonna say good-bye
我不打算跟你道e
or anything sappy like that.
整多愁善感那一套
You know how I feel.
你懂我的感X
Okay.
就@影
You know, I didn't know where you were the last four hours.
我不知道你@四小r去哪里了
I know.
我知道
I'm sorry.
Σ黄
I thought you ran off to Mexico
我以槟闩艿侥西哥城
and abandoned the kids.
不要孩子了
I would never run off to Mexico
我永h不跑到墨西哥城
and abandon the kids without you.
G下你和孩子
Promise?
你保C
I promise.
我保C
I can't stop thinking about the one we lost, Jack.
我忍不住去想我失去的那孩子  杰克
I can't. I know...
我一直想  我知道
I know we have these new babies, and I should be happy,
我知道有了@些新生  我_心才
but I just can't stop thinking about him.
但我就是忍不住去想他
Me, too.
我也是
- Yeah? ?- Yeah.
-是  -是
That's all I think about.
我MX子都是@事
I feel... ?
我感X
I feel guilty when I think about him,
我想到他r  感X很染
and then, you know, I-I feel guilty
然后  不想他r
when I stop thinking about him.
也感X很染
Me, too.
我也是
I thought it was just me.
我以橹挥形疫@酉
No. It's me, too.
不  我也@酉
I love you.
我勰
I love you, too.
我也勰
I think we need to give him a new name.
我得o他起新名字
I think it's important.
我X得@很重要
Where'd you get that idea?
你怎么@么想
I just thought of it.
就是@么感X的
Come in.
M
I'm sorry today didn't go as we hoped.
很抱歉今天不如想象中利
I'm not done yet, though.
但我不就此放
There's more than one big-shot oncologist in New York.
~s不只有一害的[瘤＜
Okay.
好
I'd like to tell the girls who you are.
我想跟孩子f出你的身份
I was thinking maybe first thing tomorrow.
我想明天一早就f
They'll have a lot of questions.
她有很多疑
Whatever they want to know.
我一定知o不言
Okay.
好
How'd you meet my mother?
你跟我怎么JR的
On a bus, of all places.
你都想不到  在巴士上JR的
My God, she looked beautiful.
天  她r可美了
And let me tell you...
我告V你...
You okay?
你]事吧
Yeah, he's okay.
]事  他很好
I'm okay.
我很好
Hey, sweet boy.
H鄣男
You want to try?
你想
Hi, Randall... Hi.
m德  你好呀
ZiMuZu.tv
字幕M